练习 2-18：练习意群。这次我读这段话时，会
Exercise 2-18, Practicing Word Groups. When I read the paragraph this time, I'll
夸张停顿。虽然我们现在练的是意群，但记住，
exaggerate the pauses. Although we're working on word groups here, remember, I
我不希望你丢掉语调。跟我重复每个句子组。
don't want you to lose your intonation. Repeat each sentence group after me.
Hello. My name is Anne. I'm taking American accent training. There's a lot to
learn, but I hope to make it as enjoyable as possible. I should pick up on the
American intonation pattern pretty easily although the only way to get it is to
practice all the time. I use the up and down or peaks and valleys intonation more
than I used to. I've been paying attention to pitch too. It's like walking down a
staircase. I've been talking to a lot of Americans lately and they tell me that I'm
easier to understand. Anyway I could go on and on, but the important thing is to listen
听起来不错。嗯，你觉得呢？我做到了吗？接下来练习这些意群。
well and sound good. Well, what do you think? Do I? Next, practice the word
用强语调读三遍。朗读时，停顿要自然，
groups three times using strong intonation. When reading, your pauses
不应该长，也不应该戏剧化，只要足够让听者有时间
should be neither long nor dramatic, just enough to give your listener time to
消化你所说的内容。一定要按每个短语吸气，而不是按每个
digest what you're saying. Be sure to take a breath for each phrase, not for each
词，当然也不是整段只吸一次。
word, or indeed the entire paragraph.